hi everybody this song is called the
Tower of Babel and it's about when you
get too big too high you're bound to
come crashing down
[Music]
once you smoke just one language lived
out on the eastern plain
houses of stone and mortar
at the beginning of the world
[Music]
we said come let us build ourselves a
city the tower the beaches to heaven ma
Eastern plane
names
[Music]
[Applause]
we will be one people
[Music]
one language one reason
got a son me of the season know the
limits up a flash when hours scattered
to all corners of the earth battling
tons of unreason
the tower remains a finnish architect
mr. blasters mission to pay July
[Music]
[Applause]
- I
just like another Tower of Babel
don't make sense anymore
so Mason
[Music]
come let us be gods of reason
my Venus
ships up titanium baby die
[Music]
there's nothing but cold space
Stalin television
we are creatures of yours real
divergent tongue
[Music]
[Applause]
so come let us make ourselves
rock-and-roll band
I'll tear their breasts
yes
so he took a bricks and I time we built
ourselves a great tower
lordy looked upon us
to be
ah
Pass
to be
- hi just like a town Bible
don't make sense
[Music]
yes